{
    question: "Where did the first Rubik's Cube competition was organized?",
    choice1:  "Brazil",
    choice2:  "Budapest",
    choice3:  "Paris",
    choice4:  "Boston",
    answer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "What did the Rubik's Cube manufacturer consider naming the cube for its international launch in 1980?",
    choice1:  "It was always going to be called Rubik's Cube",
    choice2:  "The Gordian Knot",
    choice3:  "The Wonder Cube",
    choice4:  "Puzzling Puzzle",
    answer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "Who set an official world record time for solving the 3x3x3 Rubik's Cube? How fast was that record?",
    choice1:  "Feliks Zemdegs 7.95 seconds",
    choice2:  "Lucas Etter 4.93 seconds",
    choice3:  "Minh Thai 22.95 Seconds",
    choice4:  "Erno Rubik 24.22 seconds",
    answer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "How many PLL Cases are there in CFOP method of solving Rubik's Cube",
    choice1:  "51",
    choice2:  "27",
    choice3:  "21",
    choice4:  "12",
    answer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the first cuber to get a sub 4 in an official competition?",
    choice1:  "Max Park",
    choice2:  "Feliks Zemdegs",
    choice3:  "Yusheng du",
    choice4:  "Aryan Chabbra",
    answer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "In what year skewb was declared an official wca event?",
    choice1:  "2012",
    choice2:  "2006",
    choice3:  "2014",
    choice4:  "2018",
    answer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "Which cuber dropped the cube while solving and still got a sub 5 solve in an offical WCA competition?",
    choice1:  "Sebastian Weyer",
    choice2:  "Chris Olson",
    choice3:  "Patrick Ponce",
    choice4:  "Jayden McNeill",
    answer: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "Choose the most used speedcubing method?",
    choice1:  "CFOP",
    choice2:  "Roux",
    choice3:  "Petrus",
    choice4:  "ZZ",
    answer: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Who holds the asian record for 3x3 OH (single) event?",
    choice1:  "Bhargav Narasimhan",
    choice2:  "Asia Konvittayayotin",
    choice3:  "Ruihang Xu",
    choice4:  "Max Park",
    answer: 2,
  },

  {
    question: "which cuber won the WCA World Championship twice?",
    choice1:  "Max Park",
    choice2:  "Yusheng Du",
    choice3:  "Kevin Hays",
    choice4:  "Feliks Zemdegs",
    answer: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "Where was the World Rubik's Cube Championship was held in 2019",
    choice1:  "Paris, France",
    choice2:  "Beijing, China",
    choice3:  "Melbourne, Australia",
    choice4:  "SÃ£o Paulo, Brazil",
    answer: 3,
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the world record holder for rubiks cube with feet event?",
    choice1:  "Mohammed Aiman Koli",
    choice2:  "Henri Gerber",
    choice3:  "Daniel Rose-Levine",
    choice4:  "Tommy Cherry",
    answer: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Who invented CFOP method of solving 3x3x3 Rubik's Cube?",
    choice1:  "Jessica Fredrich",
    choice2:  "Ron Van Bruchem",
    choice3:  "Minh Thai",
    choice4:  "Erik Akkersdijk",
    answer: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "The book 'The Winning Solution' teaches which method?",
    choice1:  "CFOP",
    choice2:  "Roux",
    choice3:  "Ortega",
    choice4:  "Ortega Corners-First",
    answer: 4,
  },

  {
    question: "In which year WCA was formed?",
    choice1:  "2000",
    choice2:  "2002",
    choice3:  "2003",
    choice4:  "2007",
    answer: 3,
  },